windowsphone7series.com 2017-10-28

# Privacy and Terms - Windows Phone Home

At WindowsPhone7Series.com we want our users to have the best experience possible, which is why your privacy is very important to us. By using this website you agree to be bound by the privacy policy and terms as set out below.

**Your Information**

By using this website, you agree that we may collect non-personally identifiable information from you – this includes data such as the browser you are using, screen resolution and so on. None of this information can personally identify you or will provide us with any information such as who you are, email address, etc.

If you sign up to become an insider or use our contact form then you will be asked for your e-mail address. This will be used only to contact you for the reasons specified and will not be sold or given to any third parties. If you wish for us to remove your email address then please use the [contact form](https://www.windowsphone7series.com/backstage/) to get in touch.

If we collect non-personally identifiable information from you then this is only used for analytical purposes, in order to help improve our website. Again, this data will not be sold or given to any third parties.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data that allow web pages to remember your preferences when browsing. By using this website you agree to the use of cookies, but these can be turned off at any time using your browser settings. We use cookies to get a better idea of the pages you browse using the site and to sometimes tailor advertisements through partners such as Google Ads. We do not have any access to personal information through the use of cookies.

**Third Party Sites**

We may link out to third party websites on WindowsPhone7Series.com at any time. Linking to these other websites are not endorsements of the quality of their website or their content. We will not be held responsible for any content or issues that arise from using these third party websites. Please make sure you read through the privacy policy, terms and conditions, and any other policies before browsing their site.

**Changing Our Policy**

We reserve the right to make changes to these terms and conditions, and privacy policy, at any point without prior warning. Please check this page regularly for updates.

Last updated: 15th May 2016
